A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1948-1999, bulk 1957-1997; Series 1; (Boxes 1-23, 191, OVs 233-236; 24.6 linear feet)
  - The Baltimore Museum of Art, 1958-1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Barceló, Miquel, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Barceló, Miquel, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Barr, Alfred H., Jr. (Museum of Modern Art); NYC, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Barry, Robert, 1988-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Barry, Robert - Agreement with Giuseppe Panza di Biumo, circa 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bart, Robert, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Basanese, Nadia - Loan, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bayonne Jewish Community Center, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Begneaud, Roland, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Benenkapp, John, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bellamy, Richard (Green Gallery), 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Benenson, Thomas H., 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Benesch, Edward M.; Baltimore, MD, 1958-1960, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bergman, Edwin A.; Chicago, Ill., 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Betty Chamberlain Associates, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bianchini Gallery, 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bianchini Gallery - Editions des Massons, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Billeter, Erika (Kunstgewerbe Museum); Zurich, Switzerland, 1965, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Birmingham Museum of Art; Birmingham, Alabama, 1961, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bischofberger, Bruno, 1971-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Blell, Dianne, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Blind Spot Magazine, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Blinken, Donald (and Judy) M.; NYC, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bluhm, Norman, 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - BMW (Guy Loudmer, Herve Poulain), 1975-1980; 2 Folders (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - Boatto, Alberto; Rome, Italy, 1964-1965, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bolton and Fairhead Ltd.; London, England, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bontecou, Lee, 1960-1967, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bontecou, Lee - Damaged Art Work, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bontecou, Lee - The Denver Art Museum, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bontecou, Lee - Stadtisches Museum of Leverkusen, 1967-1968; (Removed material housed in Box 191, Folder 4) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Boulois, M/M Marcel; Paris, France, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Museum Boymans-Van Beuningen; Rotterdam, Netherlands, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Brach, Paul, 1957-1959, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bradley, Harry L.; Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bright, David; Beverly Hills, Calif., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Briscoe, Eve, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Brodsky, Bernard; NYC, 1959-1975 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Brown, James, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Brown, James, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Brown, James, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Brown, James - Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Brown, James - Prices, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Brown, James - Returned Works, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Brown, J. Carter (National Gallery of Art); Washington, D.C., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Brown University, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Buckwalter, Chas and Susan, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bundy Art Gallery, 1963, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Burden, Carter and Amanda; NYC, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Byron Gallery, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - C, 1954-1969 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - C, 1970-1976 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - C, 1977-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cabot, Lewis; Boston, Mass., 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cage, John, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Calle, Sophie, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation, 1963-1964; (Removed material housed in Box 191, Folder 5) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Canaday, John (Art Critic - N.Y. Times), 1961, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Art; Ontario, Canada, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cane, Louis, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Capogrossi, Giuseppe (Artist), 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Institute (Museum of Art), 1957-1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cart and Crate; Los Angeles, Calif., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Castelli, Barbara (Bertozzi), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1957-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1966-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1977, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1978; (Oversized material housed in OV 233) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1980, January-June (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1980, July-December (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1981, January-September (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1981, October-December (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1982, January-April (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1982, May-December (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Castelli, Leo, circa 1990s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1991, January-June (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1991, July-December (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1992, January-February (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1992, March-July (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1992, August-December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Castelli, Leo, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Castelli, Leo - 30th Anniversary Congratulation Letters, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Castelli, Leo - Birthday, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Castelli, Leo - Birthday, circa 1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Castelli, Leo - Birthday, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, circa 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, circa 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, circa 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1988; 2 Folders (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1992; 4 Folders (Box 6, Folder 19-22)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1998-1999; 2 Folders (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
  - Castelli, Leo - Christmas Cards, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Castelli, Leo - New Year's, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Castelli, Leo - The New York Times, 1966; (Removed material housed in Box 191, Folder 6) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Castelli, Leo - Summer, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Castelli, Leo - Summer, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, California, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, Europe (Summer), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, London, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands (May), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Castelli, Leo - Travel, South America (Sept-Oct), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Castelli, Leo - Washington, D.C. Trip, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cato, Bob, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Cauduro, Ed; Portland, Ore., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Cavaglieri, Giorgio (Architect), 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - CBS Television Stations, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Centre Beaubourg; Paris, France, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Centre d'Arts Plastiques Contemporains de Bordeaux, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Centre National d'Art Contemporain, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Chamberlain, John, 1960-1974, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Chamberlain, John - Museum of Contemporary Art; Chicago, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Chamberlain, John - Questions, circa 1967-1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Channel 13; NYC, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons; NYC, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - The Chase Manhattan Bank; NYC, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Chatham College; Pittsburgh, Penn., 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Checkerboard Foundation - Joint Ventures, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cheltenham Township Art Centre, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Child Study Association of America, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Christmas, Doug; Vancouver, Canada, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Cimaise; Paris, France, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cinader, Arthur [Pollock]; Passaic, NJ, 1960-1964 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Cirker's Hayes Storage Warehouse, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1957-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Clert, Iris; Paris, France (Gallery), 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Cleveland Contemporary, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - The Cleveland Museum of Art, 1960-1974 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cohen, Arthur A.; NYC, 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Collectors Gallery, Inc.; Miami, Florida, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Collinet, Simone (Galerie Furstenbery); Paris, France, 1956-1961 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Cologne Art Faire; Germany, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Colorcraft Lithographers, Inc.; NYC, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Columbia Museum of Art, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Columbia University, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - The Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts, 1959-1973 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Contemporanea, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - The Contemporary Arts Center; Cincinnati, OH, 1966-1975, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Contemporary Arts Center - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Copley, William and John Ployardt, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Corcoran, James (James Corcoran Gallery), 1974-1978, 1990-1997 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art; Washington, D.C., 1958-1960, 1969, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art - Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom/Warren, Inc., 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Cornell, Joseph, 1956-1958, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Cornell University (Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art); NY, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Craig, Martin (Artist), 1957-1962 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Crone, Hans-Rainer; Hamburg, Germany, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Crozier Fine Arts, Inc., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - D, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - D, 1970-1990 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Daedalus Concepts, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - The Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1965-1975, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - D'Amelio Terras, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Daniel Goldreyer, Ltd., 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Weinberg Gallery; San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Daphnis, Nassos, 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Daphnis, Nassos, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Daphnis, Nassos - Damaged Art Work, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Darboven, Hanne, 1973-1976, 1980, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Letters as Artwork, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Letters as Artwork, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Letters as Artwork, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Letters as Artwork, 1987-1995; (Oversized material housed in OV 234) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Oversized Material (Letters as Artwork), 1972-1987; (Oversized material housed in OV 235) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Das Kunstwerk; Baden-Baden, Germany, 1963-1967; (Removed material housed in Box 191, Folder 7) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dartmouth College (Hopkins-Center Art Galleries), 1960-1966, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - David Gibbs and Co., Ltd.; London, England, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - David Mirvish Gallery; Toronto, Canada, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Roger Davidson; Toronto, Canada, 1964-1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Douglas - Newsweek, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Davis, Ron, 1968-1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Ron - Damages, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dayton Art Institute, 1957-1967 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Dayton's Gallery 12; Minneapolis, Minn., 1965, 1968-1969, 1973-1975; (Oversized material housed in OV 236) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - de Antonio, Emile, 1958-1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - de Bloe, Serge, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - de Bruyn, Guy; Brussels, Belgium, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Delaunay, Sonia, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - De Menil Family; Houston, Texas, 1962-1983 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Denney, Alice (Mrs. George C.); Washington, D.C., circa 1960s (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - The Denver Art Museum, 1969-1993 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Des Moines Art Center; Des Moines, Iowa, 1960-1976, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts; Detroit, Mich., 1964-1974, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - DeWitt Stern, Gutmann and Co., Inc. (Insurance); NYC, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Diamonstein, Barbaralee, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Dibbets, Jan, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Dilexi Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Dine, Jim, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Documenta III, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Documenta IV, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Documenta IV, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Documenta V, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Documenta GmbH, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Dolph, Norman; NYC, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Domus; Milan, Italy, 1961-1966 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Dorazio, Piero, 1956-1962 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Dorfles, Gillo (Writer-Art critic); Milan, Italy, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Dotremont, Philippe; Brussels, Belgium, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - The Douglas S. Cramer Company; Los Angeles, Calif., 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Douglas Drake Gallery; Kansas City, Kansas, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - The Douglas Gallery, Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Drouin, René, 1956-1968 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Dunkelman Gallery; Canada, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - The Dunn International Exhibition; London, England, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Durable Dish Company, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Dwan Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Dwan Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Dzubas, Friedel, 1958-1966 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - E, 1958-1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - E, 1970-1982, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - East Hampton Gallery, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Editions Alecto Limited, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Eisenstein, Julian, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Eisner, Eugene, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Elkon, Robert, 1959-1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Epstein, Mrs. Henry (Eddie); NYC, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Escobar, Marisol, 1957-1962; (Oversized material housed in OV 237) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Escobar, Marisol - N.W. Ayer and Son, Inc.; Philadelphia, Pa., 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Estorick, Eric; London, England, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Everett Ellin Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Everson Museum of Art; NY, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. (E.A.T.), 1968-1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - F, 1956-1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - F, 1970-1983 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - F, 1984-1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Factor, Donald; Los Angeles; London, 1961-1971 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Falzoni, Giordano; Rome, Italy, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - FAR Gallery, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Felluss Gallery Group, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Ferus Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Ferus Gallery; Los Angeles, Calif., 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ferus Gallery - Roy Lichtenstein, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Ferus Gallery - Frank Stella, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Festa Printing; NYC, 1959, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Finch College Museum; NYC, 1959, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Fischmann, Milton, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Fisher, Ray - Negative and Contact Sheets, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Flash Art, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1979-1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Flavin, Dan, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Flavin, Dan - Certificates, 1979-1996 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Flavin, Dan - Pierre Huber, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Flavin, Dan - Michael Jaspan, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Flavin, Dan - Pending, 1970-1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Flavin, Dan - Stoker Sale, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Flint Institute of Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Florsheim, Lillian H.; Chicago, Ill., 1960-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fogg Art Museum, 1964-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Ford Foundation, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Forge, Andrew, 1966, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fort Worth Art Center, 1966-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Foundation Arc-en-ciel, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, Inc.; NYC, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Foundation Maeght, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fourcade, Xavier, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Francés, Esteban, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Fratelli Fabbri Editori, 1968-1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Freeman, Mrs. Stanley (Betty); Beverly Hills, Calif., 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Freie Galerie; Germany, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Frenkel and Co., Inc.; NYC, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Friedman, B. H.; NYC, 1953-1964, 1969, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Friedrich, Heiner, 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Froehlich, J. W., 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Furniture Shipments, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Futterman, A. Leon (Accountant - Steinfeld and Futterman), 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - G, 1956-1965 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - G, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - G, 1969-1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - G, 1977-1983 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Gablik, Suzi (Art critic), 1961, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Gagosian, Larry; Los Angeles, Calif., 1982, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Gaines, Charles, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Galerie 22 (J. P. Wilhelm); Dusseldorf, Germany, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Galerie Aronowitsch, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Galerie Beyeler; Basle, Switzerland, 1959-1983, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Galerie Beyeler - Roy Lichtenstein, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Galerie Bruno Bischofberger; Zurich, Switzerland, 1969, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Galerie Bruno Bischofberger - Miquel Barceló Consignment, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Galerie Buren; Stockholm, Sweden, 1967-1976 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Galerie Claude Bernard (Claude Bernard Haim); Paris, France, 1959-1965, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Galerie Daniel Cordier; Paris, France, 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Galerie de Gestlo, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Galerie Francoise Mayer, 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Galerie Handschin, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Galerie Karl Flinker; Paris, France, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Galerie Kriwin; Bruxelles, Belgium, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Galerie Louis Carré; Paris, France, 1956-1964 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Galerie M; Bochum; Weitmar, Germany, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Galerie Nachst St. Stephan, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Galerie Ricke (Rolf Ricke); Kassel and Cologne, Germany, 1965-1979 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Galerie Rive Droite; Paris, France, 1958-1969 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Galerie Rudolfe Zwirner; Cologne, Germany, 1963-1973 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Galerie Saqqârah (Georges Marci); Gstaad, Switzerland, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Galerie Schmela (Alfred Schmela); Dusseldorf, Germany, 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Galerie Springer (Rudolf Springer); Berlin, Germany, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Galerie Stadler, 1957-1969 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Galerie Thomas Borgmann, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Galleria Apollinaire, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Galleria d'Arte del Naviglio (Carlo Cardazzo); Milan, Italy, 1956-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Galleria Dell'Ariete; Milan, Italy, 1961-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Galleria l'Elefante, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Galleria Rubbers (Director: Natalio Jorge Povarché); Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Galleria Toninelli Arte Moderna; Milan, Italy, 1961-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Galleri Ostergren; Sweden, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gana Art Gallery; Seoul, Korea [Roy Lichtenstein], 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ganz, Sally and Victor; NYC, 1963-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Garfield, Gil, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Geldzahler, Henry, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gemini G.E.L., Ltd.; Los Angeles, Calif., 1967-1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Genova, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - George Peabody College (Art Dept.); Nashville, Tenn., 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Gertrude Kasle Gallery; Detroit, Mich., 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Getz, Ilse, circa 1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Gian Enzo Sperone Arte Moderna; Torino, Italy, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Gilbreath, Nancy, 1958-1963 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Glaser, Mary Todd; NYC, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Goeteborgs Konstmuseum, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)